Henry-Russell Hitchcock
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Chronological Name and Subject Files, 1919-1987, Series 2:; (Boxes 1-22; 21.9 linear ft.)
  Segre, Maria (1963)
  Seiberling, Frank (1952, 1955-1956, 1958, 1963)
  Sekler, E. F. (1953)
  Sekler, Edward F. (1976)
  Sekler, Edward L. (1960, 1965-1967)
  Seligman, Georges E. (1950)
  Sellin, David (1972)
  Selz, Peter (1959-1960)
  Senie, Harriet (1976, 1979, 1981)
  Senter, Terance A. (1972, 1974)
  Serynyk, Peter (1966, 1973)
  Sert, Jose Luis (1954, 1956)
  Seven Arts Book Society (1957)
  Severini, Lois (1978-1979, 1982-1984)
  Seymour, Anne Halle (1966)
  Seznec, Jean (1955)
  Shaker Community, Hancock, Mass. (1962)
  Shapira, Nathan, H. (1961)
  Shapiro, Ellen R. (1977)
  Shapiro, Meyer (1961)
  Shaw, Thomas S. (1966)
  Shawe-Taylor, Desmond (1946)
  Shawmut Bank (1954)
  Shea, Mrs. John L. (1954)
  Shear, John K. (1956)
  Sheffield, Margaret (1974)
  Shelter Publications (1973)
  Shepley, Bullfinch, Richardson and Abbott (1961, 1981)
  Shepley, Henry (1948)
  Sheraton Hotel (1952, 1968)
  Sheridan, Friede (1956-1959, 1961)
  Sherwood, Mrs. John R. (1952)
  Shillaber, Caroline (1957, 1972)
  Shipley, Brown (undated)
  Shipman, Mary (1965)
  Shipman, Mary and Arthur (1956)
  Shoe String Press, Inc. (1965, 1979)
  Shokokusha Publications (1961)
  Shore, James R. (1962)
  Shores, Ken (1962)
  Sias, Garrett K. (1959)
  Sidles, Mrs. Frank C. (1963)
  Sihriu, Omico (1955)
  Silsby, Peter (1961)
  Silverman, Jill Anne (1975)
  Silvermine Publications (1965)
  Simpson, Charles (1968)
  Simpson, Mrs. Kenneth F. (1950)
  Simpson, Marc (1977)
  Simpson, P. L. (1973)
  Sims, W. S. (1946)
  Simson, Otto G. (1954)
  Singelenberg, Pieter (1962-1963, 1970-1971, 1974)
  Singleton, W. A. (1956)
  Sinnen, Jean (1964)
  Sise, Hazen (1969)
  Sitwell, Gilbert (1952)
  Sizer, Theodore (1933, 1945-1946, 1950-1952, 1956, 1963)
  Skempton, A.W. (1961)
  Skidmore, Owings and Merrill (1960-1963, 1979)
  Skopek, Thomas (1949)
  Sky, Alison (1975)
  Slater Memorial Museum (1950)
  Sleepy Hollow Restorations (1957)
  Slive, Seymour (1958)
  Slive, Zoya (1965)
  Sloan, Joseph C. (1959)
  Sloane, Joseph C. (1958)
  Small, Philip L. (1928)
  Smartt, Donald (1981)
  Smith, Alexander Mackay (1949) (see also: Mackay-Smith, Alexander)
  Smith and Sons (1953)
  Smith, Anna L. (undated)
  Smith, Betty (1928-1929)
  Smith College (1946-1964, 1966-1973, 1975-1976, 1978, 1981-1982) (see also: Department; Kennedy Fund)
  Smith College Alumnae Association (1954) (see also: Alumnae Association)
  Smith, E. Baldwin (1946-1947, 1953)
  Smtih, Edith (1928-1929)
  Smith, Fred S. (1928)
  Smith, Mrs. Frederick (1945)
  Smith, G. E. Kidder (1957, 1961, 1963, 1965)
  Smith, George Walter Vincent Museum (1961)
  Smith, Gertrude D. (1972)
  Smith, Hinchman and Grulls Associates, Inc. (1976)
  Smith, Kathryn (1976-1980, 1983, 1986)
  Smith, Linn (1947)
  Smith, Meg (1972, 1974)
  Smith, Patricia Anne (1950)
  Smith, Peter van der Meulen (1927-1928)
  Smith, Robert C. (1950-1952, 1956)
  Smith, Sidney (1947)
  Smith, Vincent (1971)
  Smith, William and Son (1949)
  Smithson, Peter (1966)
  Smithsonian Associates (1975)
  Smithsonian Institution (1967, 1976, 1979)
  Smyser, H. M. (1965)
  Smyth, Craig Hugh (1951-1952, 1956, 1983)
  Snow, Florence (1955)
  Snow, Wilbert (1945)
  Snowden, Ernest (1927-1928)
  Snyder, John (1974)
  Soby, James Thrall (1945-1950, 1954-1955, 1957-1958, 1960-1961, 1968, 1977, 1979)
  Soby, Nellie (1951-1953)
  Societe Editions de France (1958)
  Society for the Preservation of Long Island Antiquities (see: Long Island Antiquities, Society for the Preservation of)
  Society for the Preservation of New England Antiquities (1948, 1972, 1975) (see also: New England Antiquities, Society for the Preservation of; Preservation of New England Antiquities, Society for the)
  Society of Architectural Historians (1949-1985, 1987)
  Society of Architectural Historians of Great Britain (1958-1980, 1983-1986)
  Society of Mayflower Descendants (see: Mayflower Descendants, Society of)
  Solomon, Arthur and Marny (1975)
  Solomon, Pringle (1948)
  Somerset Co. [N.J.] Park Commission (1970)
  Somerwil, J. (1962)
  Sommer, Clifford C. (1958)
  Sommer, Frank (1970)
  Sonne, Fi (1955-1956)
  Sonnenberg, Benjamin (1972)
  Sorem, Lucia (1961)
  Soria, Martin (1958)
  Sotheby Parke Bernet, Inc. (1971, 1982)
  Southern California, University of (1966, 1968)
  Southern Regional Education Board (1966)
  Spaeth, John W. (1945-1946)
  Spark, Victor (1948, 1971)
  Spear, Dorothea (1955)
  Speed Art Museum (see: Louisville, J. B. Speed Art Museum)
  Speed, Herbert (1946)
  Speirs, Bruce (1982)
  Spence, Basil (1963-1964)
  Spence, Eleanor (1954)
  Spencer, Brian (1973-1974)
  Spencer, Stephen (1956)
  Spencer, Walter L. (1975-1976, 1978)
  Sperling, Harry G. (1955)
  Speyer, Darthea (1952)
  Spokes, P. S. (1955)
  Sprague, Joan Forrester (1960)
  Sprague, Paul (1973, 1980, 1983)
  Springarn, J. E. (1938)
  Springfield [Mass.] (1980-1981)
  Springfield [Mass.] City Planning Department (1971)
  Springfield [Mass.] Museum of Fine Arts (1949, 1954)
  Springfield [Mass.] Republican (1944-1945)
  Springfield [Miss.] Art Museum (1949)
  Staatsarchiv (1966)
  Stabile, Elizabeth (1963)
  Stadt Koln (1957)
  Stahl, Frederick A. (Tod) (1969-1970)
  Staib, Hermann (1966, 1968-1969, 1974)
  Staley, Karl A. (1953)
  Stamm, Gunther (1979)
  Stamp, Gavin (1978, 1985)
  Stanford University (1985)
  Stanton, Phoebe B. (1952-1954, 1958, 1965, 1968, 1970)
  Staples Press (1950)
  Starr, Mrs. Nathan C. (1952)
  State Department, U. S. (1955, 1956, 1958) (see also: Department of State; United States Department of State)
  State Department, U.S. Information Agency (1957)
  State Historical Society of Wisconsin (see: Wisconsin, State Historical Society of)
  Stebbins, Theodore E. (1965-1969, 1972-1973, 1977-1978)
  Steegman, John (1950-1952, 1955-1956)
  Steele, Geoffrey (1946, 1948, 1953)
  Steen Hasselbalchs Forlag (1962)
  Stein, Donna (1973-1974, 1978-1979)
  Stein, Joseph A. (1947)
  Stein, Margaret (1949)
  Stein, Roger B. (1960)
  Steiner, Johannes (1966)
  Steinway and Sons (1946)
  Steinway, Cassie (1960-1961, 1976, 1979, 1983-1985, undated)
  Steinway, Cassie and Federick (1954)
  Steinway, Frederick (1974)
  Steinway, Lydia (1952-1953)
  Steinway, Ruth (1928, 1945, 1947, 1949-1950, 1955-1956, 1958-1963, 1965-1968, 1970-1971, 1973-1974, 1978)
  Steinway, Ruth and Theodore D. (1952-1954)
  Steinway, Theodore D. (1982)
  Steliaros, Mary (1974)
  Stephens, Sherrie L. (1962)
  Stern (1979)
  Stern, Edgar (1977)
  Stern, Edgar and Bita (1975)
  Stern, Robert (1964, 1975, 1984-1985)
  Sterner, Harold (1947)
  Sternfeld, Fred and Sophia (1946-1957, 1959-1964, 1966, 1968, 1978, 1985-1986)
  Sternfeld, Sophia (1970)
  Stetson, Eugene W. (1965)
  Stevens and Brown (1946)
  Stevens, Sam (1964)
  Stevens, Samuel (Thomas) (1953-1954)
  Steyer, Glenn (1978)
  Stiles, Florence Ward (1949-1950)
  Sting, Hellmut (1966)
  Stirling, James (1953)
  Stockwell, E. Sidney (1960)
  Stoddard and Talbot (1941, 1950, 1953, 1956, 1975)
  Stoddard, Whitney (1952, 1054)
  Stoedtner, Franz (1956-1958, 1964, 1970)
  Stoller, Ezra (1956-1957, 1960)
  Stone and Downer (1946)
  Stony Point Folk Art Gallery (1957)
  Stora Co. (1949)
  Storrer, William Allin (1971-1978, 1980)
  Stott, Eric (1982)
  Stout, George L. (1953)
  Stowe-Day Foundation (1965)
  Stowell, Robert F. (1949)
  Strache, Wolf (1963)
  Strachey, John (1945)
  Straight, Stephen M. (1966, 1970)
  Straka, Paul (1974)
  Strand, Janann (1976)
  Stratton, Julius Adams (1963)
  Strauss, Irma (1982)
  Strickland, Charles R. (1938, 1948, 1955, 1957, 1959, 1961, 1963, 1966-1967, 1979)
  Stroheim and Romann (1965)
  Stroock, Paul A. (1969)
  Stroud, Dorothy (1949-1953, 1955-1964, 1966-1967, 1971, 1973, 1978, 1983, undated)
  Struck, Paul (1948)
  Stubbins, Hugh (1952, 1960)
  Stubblebine, James H. (1959, 1967-1968)
  Stubbs, Mr. and Mrs. (1986)
  Studio Books (1960-1961)
  Studio Publications (1927-1928)
  Stulz, Dale W. (1981)
  Sturbridge Village (1966-1976)
  Sturges, W. K. (1952)
  Sturges, Walter Knight (1969-1970)
  Sturm, Martha (1967)
  Stuttgart (1956, 1963)
  Suffness, Rita (1977)
  Summerson, John (1936-1937, 1939, 1941, 1945-1949, 1952-1954, 1956, 1958, 1960-1962, 1966-1967, 1969-1970, 1980, 1982)
  Sun [Baltimore] 1952 (see also: Baltimore Sun)
  Sunderland, Elizabeth (1946)
  Sunderland, John (1953)
  Sutherland, A. M. (1962)
  Sutton, Mrs. Harvey P. (1941)
  Swan, C. P. (1954)
  Swarthmore College (1928, 1939, 1945)
  Swayze, H. (1959)
  Sweeney, James Johnson (1954, 1960)
  Sweeney, Mr. and Mrs. James Johnson (1967)
  Sweeney, John (1949, 1952-1953)
  Sweeney, Robert L. (1976, 1980)
  Sweet Briar College (1953)
  Sweet, Frederick A. ( 1946, 1948, 1954)
  Sweet, Victoria M. (1968)
  Sweetland Photographers (1950)
  Swets and Zeitlinger (1960)
  Swetzoff Gallery (1951)
  Swetzoff, Hyman (1952)
  Swinton, George (1954-1955, 1957, 1964)
  Swiss Review of World Affairs (1962)
  Sylvester, David (1955)
  Syracuse University (1976)
  Syrkus, Szymon (1929)
  Szambien, Werner (1977)
  Tafel, Edgar (1962, 1971, 1973-1975, 1979-1980)
  Tait, Alan (1966-1967)
  Talbot, Harry (1952)
  Talbott, Page (1976)
  Talkington, Melinda (1969)
  Tallmer, Jerry (1954)
  Tamms, Frederick (1971)
  Tannenbaum, Lily (1969)
  Tanennbaum, Samuel (1952-1953)
  Tate, Vernon (1947)
  Tatum, George B. (1966, 1970, 1973, 1976)
  Taube, Ivan (1975)
  Taxes (1955)
  Taylor, Fred M. (1954)
  Taylor, Helen-Louise (1936-1938, undated)
  Taylor, Lisa (1984)
  Taylor, Nicholas (1962, 1966)
  Taylor, Richard (1971)
  Taylor, Walter (1953)
  Tchelitchew, Paul (1952)
  Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association (1946, 1948, 1954, 1956, 1962)
  Technische Hochschule, Darmstadt (see: Darmstadt, Technische Hochschule)
  Technology Christian Association (1949)
  Teel, William E. (1955)
  Teichmann, Maurice (1956)
  Teitelbaum Holdings, Ltd. (1982)
  Tembo, Allan (1952)
  Temple Hoyle-Buell Center for the Study of American Architecture, Columbia University (see: Columbia University, Temple Hoyle-Buell Center...)
  Temple University, Tyler School of Art (1962)
  Tendler, Max (1962)
  Tenko, Allen (1963)
  Terrestris Greenhouses (1970)
  Terry, Laurence (1952)
  Texas Co. (1954)
  Texas, University of (1968)
  Thames and Hudson, Ltd. (1961, 1967-1968, 1970, 1972)
  Thevoz, Michel (1970, 1974)
  Thirteen, WNET (1978)
  Thom, Mary (1955-1956)
  Thomas, Downing (1949)
  Thommasini, Anthony (1984)
  Thompson, Francis (1946)
  Thompson, K. (1954)
  Thompson, Luther (1946-1948, 1950)
  Thompson, Margaret and Randall (1948, 1956)
  Thompson, Molly (1949)
  Thompson, Paul (1968)
  Thompson, R. S. (1960)
  Thomson, Virgil (1927-1928, 1937, 1945-1948, 1950-1952, 1955, 1959, 1963, 1965, 1967, 1968, 1971-1972, 1974, 1979-1981, 1983, 1986, undated)
  Thornburrow, David A. (1958)
  Thornton Society of Washington (1943)
  Ticeand Lynch (1946-1947)
  Time (1959, 1967)
  Time-Life (1946)
  Times Literary Supplement (1967)
  Tiranti, John, Ltd. (1949-1950)
  Tirion, P.D.J. (1949)
  Tobias and Co. (1946)
  Toe, Abby N. (1970)
  Toledo Museum of Art (1951, 1955)
  Tomlinson, Mrs. (1951)
  Tomlinson, Juliette (1975, 1977)
  Tonetti, Joseph (1963)
  Tongue, Sukru (1955)
  Tonny, K. (1932)
  Topeka City Beautification Association (1955)
  Torbert, Donald R. (1956, 1959, 1961)
  Toronto (1957)
  Toronto, Art Gallery of (1950-1951, 1958-1960, 1974, 1977) (see also: Art Gallery of Toronto)
  Toronto, University of (1957-1960, 1976)
  Town and Country (1946)
  Trachtenberg, Martin (1976)
  Trager, Philip (1983-1984)
  Trans-World Shipping Co. (1960)
  Trapp, Frank (1953)
  Trappes-Lomax, Michael (1954)
  Traversa de Dalt (1956)
  Treasury Department, United States (see: United States Treasury)
  Trehearne and Norman (1959-1960)
  Tremaine, Dee (1950)
  Tremaine, Emily (1951-1957, 1962, 1965, 1969)
  Trenton (1973)
  Triennale de Milano (1959)
  Trinity College (see also: Austin Art Center) (1961, 1964, 1965, 1967, 1972-1973)
  Trojan, Alina (1971)
  Truex, Van Day (1946-1947)
  Tselos, Dmitri (1943, 1946, 1956, 1958, 1961)
  Tucker and Sons, Ltd. (1954)
  Tunick, Susan (1982)
  Tunnard, Christopher (1945, 1949-1951, 1958, 1965, undated)
  Tunnard, Christopher and Lydia (1946-1948, 1975, 1981)
  Tunnard, Lydia (1956, 1963)
  Turl, Victor (1946, 1956)
  Turner, Evan (1958)
  Turner, Paul (1970, 1977, 1985)
  Tuttle Co. (1952)
  Twitchell, Ralph S. (1953)
  Twiss, Richard E. (1979)
  Tyler School of Art (see: Temple University)
  Ufford, James K. (1958)
  UNESCO (1953)
  Union College (1966, 1969)
  Union Internacional de Arquitectos (1963)
  Unitarian Association (1950)
  Unitarian Congregational Society (1945)
  Unitarian Universalist Church (1963)
  United Engineering Trustees (1947)
  United Kingdom Income Tax (1978)
  United Press Association (1955)
  United States Cultural Center, Berlin (1967)
  United States Department of the Interior (1938, 1962)
  United States Department of State (see: Department of State; State Department, U. S.)
  United States Congress, Committee on Education and Labor (see: Committee on Education and Labor, U. S. Congress)
  United States Information Service (1946, 1961)
  United States Treasury (1945, 1969)
  Unity Temple (1970)
  Universal Transcontinental Corp. (1947)
  Univesita degli Studi di Napoli (see: Napoli,
  Universita degli Studi di) (1978)
  Universita Internazionale dell'Arte (1970)
  University of Bristol (see: Bristol, University of)
  University of California at Riverside (see: Riverside, University of California at)
  University of California, San Jose State (see: California, San Jose State University)
  University of Chicago (1941, 1942) (see also: Chicago, University of)
  University of Cincinnati (see: Cincinnati, University of)
  University of Delaware (see: Delaware, University of; Winterthur Program, University of Delaware)
  University of Georgia (see: Georgia, University of)
  University of Glasgow (see: Glasgow, University of)
  University of Massachusetts (see: Massachusetts, University of)
  University of Melbourne (see: Melbourne, University of)
  University of Minnesota (see: Minnesota, University of)
  University of Nebraska (see: Nebraska, University of)
  University of New Mexico (see: New Mexico, University of)
  University of Notre Dame (see: Notre Dame, University of)
  University of Oklahoma (see: Oklahoma, University of)
  University of Oregon (see: Oregon, University of)
  University of Pennsylvania (see: Pennsylvania, University of)
  University of Pittsburgh (see: Pittsburgh, University of)
  University of Texas (see: Texas, University of)
  University of Toronto (see: Toronto, University of)
  University of Wisconsin (see: Wisconsin, University of)
  University of Witwatersrand (see: Witwatersrand, University of)
  University of York (see: York, University of)
  University Prints (1956-1959, 1962, 1964)
  Unnitzer, Petra (1983)
  Upjohn, Everared M. (1953)
  Upton, Eleanor S. (1953)
  Usonia (1983)
  Utrecht, Kunsthistorische Instituut (1962)
  Utrecht, Ryksuniversiteit te (1968)
  Valentine and Sons Ltd. (1954)
  Van Agtmaal (1958)
  Van Bolschwig, Otto A. (1954) (see also: Bolschwig, Otto A. Van)
  Van der Berg, H. M. (1962)
  Van der Poel, Priscilla (1949-1950, 1952, 1955-1956, 1958, 1960, 1962-1964, 1966, 1968-1969)
  Van Derpool, James G. (1954-1956, 1959)
  Van Eyck, Aldo (1956, 1963)
  Van Fleet, Frederick A. (1946)
  Van Gent, Arie (1957)
  Vann, James Allen (1973)
  Van Ojen (1958)
  Van Ravensway, Charles (1939, 1963, 1966)
  Van Tassel, Peter (1952-1953, 1966)
  Van Trump, James D. (1957-1959, 1961, 1965, 1969)
  Van Zanten, David T. (1965-1970, 1972-1973, 1975-1979, 1983, 1985)
  Vancouver Hotel (1954)
  Vanderbilt, Paul (1928-1930, 1941, 1945-1946, 1948-1950, 1952-1954, undated)
  Vandersall, Amy (1966, 1971-1972)
  Vanity Fair (1982)
  Varley, Lee (1946, 1948, 1954, 1979)
  Vassar College (1927, 1944-1946, 1961, 1965-1966, 1975, 1977)
  Vaughan College (1962)
  Venezuela, Universidad Central de (1967)
  Venice (1975)
  Venturi, Robert (1961, 1972)
  Verlag Schnell and Steiner (1967, 1969)
  Veronen, L. (1966)
  Victoria and Albert Museum (1946, 1948-1949, 1953, 1955-1956, 1958)
  Victorian Exhibition (1972)
  Victorian Paperback [Early Victorian Architecture in Britain] (1966)
  Victorian Society (1958, 1960-1966, 1968-1970, 1972-1980, 1985)
  Victorian Society in America (1968, 1971-1986)
  Victorian Society in America, American State Capitols Research Project (1971-1977)
  Victorian Studies (1956-1959, 1962, 1967, 1969, 1971, 1973-1974)
  Viereck, Florence (1955)
  Viereck, Peter (1949-1950, 1952-1953, 1956, 1961)
  Viereck, Peter and Anya (1955)
  View Magazine (1945)
  Villanueva, A. (1956)
  Villanueva, Carlos Raul (1955, 1957-1959, 1961)
  Villanueva, Marcel (1965)
  Viollet, Brian (1958)
  Viollet, H. Roger (1959)
  Virginia, Commonwealth of (1953, 1957)
  Virginia Museum of Fine Arts (1954, 1957)
  Virginia Quarterly Review (1960)
  Virginia, University of (1928, 1962, 1969-1970)
  Visson, Assia R. (1946-1947)
  Visual Publications Ltd. (1961)
  Vogt, Adolf Max (1975)
  Voice of America (1960, 1967)
  Volpe, Anne R. (1974)
  Von Erffa, Helmut (1948, 1952, 1955-1956, 1958, 1963, 1968)
  Von Groschwitz, Fran (1970)
  Von Groschwitz, Gustav [Von] (1945-1948, 1951-1952, 1961-1962, 1965, 1968, 1972, 1978)
  Von Klemperer, Betty (1961, 1968)
  Von Moschzisker, Berthe (1945, 1947-1951)
  Vorenkamp, A.P.H. (1952)
  Vorobiov, Mary (1954)
  Vose Galleries (1960)
  Vose, Robert C. (1949)
  Vose, S. Morton (1952)
  Vygen, Willy (1928)
  Wachs, W. C. (1937)
  Waddy, Patricia (1976)
  Wade, John (1954)
  Wade, Karen Graham (1974-1975, 1977, 1982)
  Waddington Galleries (1956)
  Wadsworth Athenaeum (1928, 1941, 1946-1948, 1958, 1963)
  Wadsworth, Cleome (1945)
  Wadsworth, Julius and Clarice (1959)
  Wagner, Gunter (1983)
  Wagner, Mary-Louise (1954)
  Walch, Nicole (1972)
  Wald, Alan (1977)
  Walker Art Center (1944-1945, 1948, 1952, 1958-1959)
  Walker, John (1928, 1965, 1977)
  Walker, Robert (1959)
  Walker, William (1946)
  Wallace, Michael Lee (1959)
  Walsh, Alice M. (1970)
  Walter, Gayle (1953)
  Walter Parrish International, Ltd. (1977)
  Walters Art Gallery (1949)
  Walters, Walter H. (1971)
  Warburg Institute (1946, 1948)
  Ward, Clarence (1943, 1945, 1947, 1952)
  War Department (1948)
  Ward, James (1980-1985)
  Warn, Robert (1972, 1974)
  Warner Burns Toan Lund (1982)
  Warners, Albert (1963)
  Warnoff, Deborah (1974)
  Warren, Geoffrey (1936)
  Warren, Richard (1974)
  Warren and Whetmore (1957)
  War Service Appointment (1942-1943)
  Wasch, William (1983)
  Washburn College (1938)
  Washburn, Gordon B. (1945, 1948-1949, 1953-1954, 1965, undated)
  Washington, Associated Students' University of (1965)
  Washington Memorial Library (1954)
  Wasmuth Antiquariat (1963-1968, 1970, 1972-1974, 1979)
  Wasserman, Mrs. Amha (1959)
  Wasserman, Jack (1961-1964)
  Waterhouse, Ellis (1952)
  Watkin, David A. (1965, 1973, 1981)
  Watrous, James (1960-1961)
  Watson, Peter (1946)
  Watson, Steven (1985-1986)
  Watts, Sarah Miles (1985)
  Waugh, Arthur (1951-1953)
  Way Forum (1963)
  Weade, Katharine H. (1947)
  Weakley, Joan (1980-1981)
  Weatherby, Mrs. J. H. (1952)
  Webb, Brian (1949-1950)
  Webb, Geoffrey (1956)
  Webb, James H. (1955)
  Webb, Ltd. (1948)
  Webber, Elroy (1949)
  Weber, Harvey A. (1939, 1952)
  Weber, Roland (1976)
  Webster, J. Carson (1941, 1949, 1954, 1966, 1970, 1972-1974)
  Webster, Sara (1983)
  Wedgewood (1954, 1958-1959, 1961-1962)
  Weese, Harry (1956)
  Weill, Betsy (1977)
  Weinberg, H. Barbara (1970, 1974, 1978, 1980)
  Weinberg, Herbert (1954)
  Weinrab, Ben (1966)
  Weinreb Ltd. (1965)
  Weirick, James (1974)
  Weisberger, Bernard A. (1979)
  Weiser, Walter (1956)
  Weisman, Winston (1951-1957, 1960-1963, 1966, 1968, 1973-1975)
  Weissburger, Herbert (1961)
  Welch and Forbes (1956-1957, 1959, 1961, 1970, 1982, 1985)
  Welch and Goodhue (1986)
  Weller, Allen S. (1955)
  Wellesley College (1945, 1947, 1952, 1954, 1958, 1969)
  Wellington, Ohio (1973)
  Wells College (1965)
  Wells, Mason B. (1957-1958)
  Wells, Ruth (1949)
  Welsh College of Advanced Technology (1962-1963, 1966)
  Wensinger, Arthur Stevens (1956, 1967)
  Wenzinger, Jerry (1961)
  Werkkunstschule Krefeld (1964-1965)
  Wesley, Richard (1980)
  Wesleyan College [Macon, Ga.] (1945)
  Wesleyan University (1935, 1937-1943, 1945-1950, 1952, 1962-1963, 1967, 1973-1979, 1981-1982, 1987) (see also: Gift)
  West, J. (1952)
  West-Taylor, John P. (1960, 1962)
  Westbrook, Shirlee (1973-1974)
  Western Reserve University (1952, 1958)
  Weyhe, E. (1928, 1941, 1949, 1952-1953)
  Wheaton College (1949, 1971)
  Wheelock, Phyllis (1958)
  Wheldon, Rupert (1927)
  Whiffen, Marcus (1950-1966, 1968,-1969, 1971, 1978, 1980)
  White House (1981, 1986)
  White, Keith E. (1959)
  White, Norval (1961)
  White, Patricia (1975)
  Whitechapel Art Gallery (1956)
  Whitehead, Philip B. (1946)
  Whitehill, Walter Muir (1951-1953, 1955, 1966, 1976)
  Whitlock and Sons (1946)
  Whitney Museum of American Art (1949-1950)
  Whitson, Jim (1948)
  Whitson Publishing Co. (1979)
  Whittesley, Julian (1949)
  Whittier, Charles H. (1970, 1973)
  Who's Who (1946-1947, 1952, 1958, 1961, 1975, 1982)
  Wichman, Douglas J. (1973)
  Wick, Peter A. (1973)
  Wickey, Thomas (1952)
  Wickiser, Ralph L. (1955)
  Wicksteed, O. H. (1956)
  Wiebenson, Dora (1965-1966, 1968-1972, 1977, 1979, 1980)
  Wiedenhoeft, Ron (1969)
  Wilbraham Place (1953, 1955, 1957, 1959-1962)
  Wildenstein, Georges (1953)
  Wiley and Sons (1948, 1966)
  Wilk, Christopher (1976, 1978)
  Wilkie, David (1951-1955, 1957-1958)
  Wilkinson (1956)
  Wilkinson, Catherine M. (1963, 1965-1966)
  Willard, Helen (1950)
  Willett, Frederick W. (1969)
  Williams, A. C. O'Malley (1961) (see also: O'Malley-Williams, A. C.)
  Williams, Arthur G. A. (1955)
  Williams, B. (1957, 1964, 1967-1968)
  Williams, Buck (1958)
  Williams College (1940, 1946, 1948-1949, 1953, 1975-1976)
  Williams College Museum of Art (1963)
  Williams, Eda Carter (1958)
  Williams, Edgar I. (1952)
  Williams, David (1975)
  Williams, Gail (1979)
  Williams, J. Ronald (1967)
  Williams, Marjory (1951)
  Williams, Richard B. (1985)
  Williams, Richmond (1960-1961, 1963)
  Williams, Ronald (1973)
  Williams, Stanley T. (1950)
  Williams, Talcott (1940)
  Williamsburg (1956-1957, 1961, 1972)
  Williamson, L. S. (1962)
  Willis, L. S. (1941)
  Willis, Peter (1964-1965)
  Wills, Royal Barry (1957)
  Willson, Mr. and Mrs. Stuart Van Vranken (1953)
  Wilmerding, John (1966, 1968)
  Wilson, A. F. Johnson (1950)
  Wilson, Arnold (1962)
  Wilson, Daphne (1951)
  Wilson, H. L. McG. (1950)
  Wilson, J. P. (1956)
  Wilson, Jean (1950, 1955)
  Wilson, Joan R. (1969)
  Wilson, John H. (1980-1984)
  Wilson, Richard G. (1971, 1973)
  Wilson, Suzanne (1975, 1978)
  Wilson, Thomas J. (1955)
  Wimpfheimer, Greta (1950)
  Winchester, Alice (1953)
  Wind, Edgar (1945-1946)
  Wingerter, Wolfgang (1981)
  Winnipeg Art Gallery Association (1959)
  Winslow House (1944-1945)
  Winslow, Philip N. (1961)
  Winslow, Ralph E. (1947)
  Winter, Robert W. (1959)
  Wintersteen, Bonnie (1952)
  Winterthur Museum (1952-1953, 1955-1957, 1959, 1961, 1964, 1969, 1983)
  Winterthur Program, University of Delaware (1954-1955)
  Winthrop and Co. (1926)
  Wichnitzer, Rachel (1951)
  Wischnitzer, Ruth (1964)
  Wisconsin State Conservation Commission for Historic Preservation (1972)
  Wisconsin, State Historical Society of (1960)
  Wisconsin, University of (1946-1947, 1963, 1967, 1977)
  Wisner, John B. (1970-1971)
  Wittamer, L. (1961, 1962)
  Wittenborn and Co. (1947, 1949-1950, 1955)
  Wittenborn, George (1967-1968)
  Wittkower Fellowship Fund (1974)
  Wittkower, Rudolph (1945, 1949, 1951-1954, 1947, 1959, 1966-1968)
  Wittler, Leila (1947, 1950)